<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<questions xmlns="http://openmentor.org.uk/opencomment.xsd">

<!-- 
Compare with the "OpenComment question on amusement.doc" file - in this
case I have tried to implement the question as closely as possible to 
the form of the original, which uses the JavaScript object model a 
bit differently. 
-->

	<question id="default">
		<text>
Study the following passage.  What does Aristotle take to be 
the place of amusement in the best life?

Happiness … is not found in amusement; for it would be absurd 
if the end were amusement, and our lifelong efforts and sufferings 
aimed at amusing ourselves. For… serious work and toiled aimed 
only at amusement appears stupid and excessively childish. Rather, 
it seems correct to amuse ourselves so that we can do something 
erious…for amusement would seem to be relaxation, and it is 
because we cannot toil continuously that we require relaxation. 
Relaxation, then, is not the end, since we pursue it to prepare 
for activity. (Nicomachean Ethics 1176b, translated by T. Irwin;
Indianapolis: Hackett 1985)
		</text>
		<segment>
			/(?:\.|\?)/
		</segment>
		
		<concepts>
			<concept name="aim" class="uk.org.opencomment.svm.SVMClassifier">
				<vocabulary>amusement,life,objective,aim,leisure,happiness,goal,serious,Aristotle,work,best,people</vocabulary>
    			<include>Amusement is not the end or objective of life</include>
    			<include>Leisure is not life's main goal</include>
    			<include>We are not here just to enjoy ourselves</include>
    			<include>Life is not only about being happy</include>
    			<include>people should not treat it as their ultimate aim</include>
    			<exclude>Something about serious work</exclude>
    			<exclude>Argument by Aristotle about being childish</exclude>
    			<exclude>Best life and amusement</exclude>
    			<exclude>Ethics is all about whether life's objectives are right</exclude>
  			</concept>
  			
  			<concept name="leisure" class="uk.org.opencomment.svm.SVMClassifier">
				<vocabulary>amusement,rest,relax,work,serious,life,objective,aim,people,Aristotle</vocabulary>
				<include>We need amusement for rest and relaxation</include>
				<include>Leisure helps us rest so we can work better</include>
				<include>Rest is is about preparing for toil and serious work</include>
				<include>Effective work depends on being able to relax</include>
				<exclude>We are not here just to enjoy ourselves</exclude>
				<exclude>Argument by Aristotle about being childish</exclude>
				<exclude>Best life and amusement</exclude>
				<exclude>Ethics is all about whether life's objectives are right</exclude>
			</concept>
		</concepts>
		
		<rules lang="text/javascript">
			if (answer.findConcept("aim")) {
				if (answer.findConcept("leisure")) {
					answer.response.addParagraph("Yes, that's right, well done");
				} else {
					answer.response.addParagraph("Good, that's right. But does Aristotle think " +
						"that amusement has any role to play in the best life?");
				}
			} else {
				if (answer.findConcept("leisure")) {
					answer.response.addParagraph("Good, that's right. But can you say a little more? " +
						"If we need amusement in order to relax, what does that imply about the " +
						"objective or purpose of our lives?");
				} else {
					answer.response.addParagraph("Have another try. Before typing in your answer, " +
						"read the passage carefully again. Does Aristotle think that amusement is " +
						"the end or objective of human life? Does he think that amusement plays any " +
						"useful role in our lives at all? ");
				}
			}
		</rules>
	</question>
</questions>